homebrewing.org 2019-02-19

# Privacy Policy / GDPR

Privacy Policy / GDPR

This Privacy Policy describes how Adventures in Homebrewing Inc. (“Adventures in Homebrewing”, “we”, “our”, or “us”) collects, uses, and shares personal information of users of this website, www.homebrewing.org (the “Site”), and users of Adventures in Homebrewing’s Services Platform (the “Platform”). We periodically update this Privacy Policy and reserve the right to change the provisions of this Policy or our privacy practices at any time. If you subscribe to Adventures in Homebrewing’s Platform, we encourage you to review this site periodically. Your use of the Site or the Platform constitutes consent to any changes in this Policy as in effect on the date of such use.

Your Rights to Access Your Personal Information. You have the right to access personal information about you that Adventures in Homebrewing has collected through this Site by sending a request for access to hops@homebrewing.org. You can also request that we correct or delete any such information by sending an email to the same address. To verify that the request is authentic, we may require that such request be sent from the email address associated with your personal information. While we will comply reasonably and promptly with your request, we may need to retain some of your information for our own record keeping or to fulfill a legal obligation.

If you have a Site customer account, you may update your account information by logging in here: Homebrewing.org Customer Login

If you are a subscriber to Adventures in Homebrewing’s Platform, you may correct, update, or remove your information by making the change on your user account settings page, or by emailing our Customer Support Team at hops@homebrewing.org. If you no longer desire our services, please contact us directly.

What is personal information?

Personal information means information that specifically identifies an individual person, such as name, mailing address, email address, phone number, or account number. It may also include other information about you, such as gender, date of birth, or other demographic information, or about your use of the Site, such as IP address or cookies, if that other information is linked to your personal information.

How is your information collected?

Adventures in Homebrewing collects personal information that you provide to us. For example:

When you make a purchase from our site, you provide your name, email address, credit card information, address, phone number, and a password. We use this information to process your orders, to keep you updated on your orders and to personalize your shopping experience. You may also be asked to create a username and password to login to our Platform. To keep you informed about our latest offers, we may notify you of current promotions, specials and new additions to HomeBrewing.org. You may unsubscribe from our newsletters by following the unsubscribe instructions in any email you receive from us.

Our website includes social media features, such as links to our Facebook, YouTube and Twitter pages. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

We also collect some of your information automatically when you visit this Site or log in. For example, this Site collects your IP address and other online identifiers and records the pages that you visit and other information about your activity on the Site.

Like many other websites, we use “cookies” to remember information about you and improve your browsing experience on our Site. We use "cookies" to keep track of your current shopping session to personalize your experience and so that you may retrieve your shopping cart at any time. We also use "cookies" to collect and analyze website statistics such as which pages are most visited and which websites and keywords drive visitors to our site. If you reject cookies, you may still use our Site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our Site may be limited. We may also work with third-parties providers who may use cookies on our Site. You can block cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. 

What do we do with your information?

Adventures in Homebrewing may use your personal information to:

  * provide products and services;
  * send requested product or service information;
  * send marketing communication;
  * send you emails or otherwise respond to questions, concerns, and customer support inquiries;
  * create demographic profiles of our subscribers, clients, and visitors to target our email alerts and website marketing; or
  * to improve the services we offer you or the functionality of our Site.

Adventures in Homebrewing does not sell personal information to third parties and does not transfer or share customers’ personal information between its clients. 

Adventures in Homebrewing will share your personal information only:

with your consent;

  * to fulfill a legal obligation, including:
  * in response to lawful requests or legal process, including in response to law enforcement requirements; or
  * as part of a business transaction, sale or transfer, or bankruptcy proceeding;
  * for protection of personal or public safety or to prevent illegal activities;
  * to protect our own rights including enforcing our own policies, contracts, and terms of use.

How does Adventures in Homebrewing Protect Personal Information?

Adventures in Homebrewing follows generally accepted standards to protect personal information and information submitted by our clients, both during transmission and once we receive it. Adventures in Homebrewing maintains all clients in carrier-class secure facilities protected by firewalls and other security devices. These measures are designed to protect visitor and client information from loss, misuse, or unauthorized alteration. Adventures in Homebrewing employs various information security mechanisms and internal policies and procedures to protect information from disclosure to unauthorized third parties. Adventures in Homebrewing routinely audits its practices and policies to meet industry standards for data protection. Adventures in Homebrewing provides an SSL encrypted, password-protected mechanism for logging in, viewing, uploading, and extracting client data on our Platform.

Personal information provided to Adventures in Homebrewing by its clients remains the property of its clients.

|  **Privacy on Other Web Sites**  
Other sites accessible through our site have their own privacy policies and data collection practices. Please consult each site s privacy policy. Adventures in HomeBrewing is not responsible for the actions of third parties.

Communicating With You

We use the information we collect about you to communicate with you, including via email, phone, sms text message or push notifications, as you decide, for reasons such as: 

  * to confirm purchases you have made through our website; 
  * to confirm that your purchases have shipped; 
  * to invite you to review purchases made via the Services; 
  * to notify you of items left in your shopping cart; 
  * to notify you when you have won a contest or sweepstakes; 
  * to notify you when we make changes to our user agreements; 
  * to fulfill a request by you; 
  * to provide you with product recommendations; 
  * to provide you with access to personalized information based on your location; 
  * to contact you about your account with us; 
  * and to offer you other products, programs or services from us and our affiliates, business partners, and selected third parties that we believe may be of interest to you. 

Legal and Law Enforcement Purposes

We may disclose personal information in response to legal process, for example in response to a court order or a subpoena, or in response to a law enforcement agency's request. We also may disclose such information to third parties in connection with fraud-scoring, detection, and prevention activities or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms & Conditions, to protect our rights and the rights of others, and as otherwise required by law.

Changes To This Policy

From time to time, we may update this Privacy Policy. We will notify you about material changes in the way we treat personal information by placing a notice on this website or by sending you an email message. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this policy so that you always will know our current privacy practices.

How To Contact Us

Customer Service & Questions

Tel: (313)-277-2739

Fax: (313)-583-3294

Email: Hops@homebrewing.org

If emailing please include your phone number if you require more than a yes/no answer. 

Then we can give you a quick call if we need more information. Thanks!

Customer Service Hours:

Monday - Friday: 10:00 am-7:00 pm

Saturday: 10:00 am-5:00 pm

Sunday: 12:00 pm-4:00 pm

Our Full Service Retail Locations

Adventures in Homebrewing - Taylor

23869 Van Born RD

Taylor, MI 48180 USA

Adventures in Homebrewing - Ann Arbor

6071 Jackson RD

Ann Arbor, MI 48103 USA
